Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2018
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer Hans Thomalla coaches student composer Seong Ae Kim at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9623.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_051.tif)
- Composer Hans Thomalla coaches student composers Igor Coelho A.S. Marques, Reilly Spitzfaden, and Seong Ae Kim at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9624.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_052.tif)
- Lucy Hatem, clarinet rehearsing Flannery Cunningham's piece We are the same as we have always been at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9626.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_053.tif)
- Flannery Cunningham coaches Lucy Hatem, clarinet on Cunningham's piece We are the same as we have always been at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9636.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_054.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor rehearses Fernando Munizaga's Ondas Primarias with Slee Sinfonietta members Jade Conlee, piano, Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Michael Matsuno, bass flute, Stephen Solook, percussion, Kristen Theriault, harp, Lucy Hatem, clarinet, and Michael Tumiel, bass clarinet at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9640.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_055.tif)
- Fernando Munizaga coaches Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Michael Matsuno, bass flute, Stephen Solook, percussion, and Kristen Theriault, harp on Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9641.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_056.tif)
- Fernando Munizaga coaches Slee Sinfonietta member Kristen Theriault, harp on Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias as Slee Sinfonietta member Stephen Solook, percussion looks on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9642.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_057.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta member Michael Matsuno, flute rehearses at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9645.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_058.tif)
- Fernando Munizaga coaches Slee Sinfonietta member Kristen Theriault, harp on Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias as Slee Sinfonietta member Michael Tumiel, bass clarinet looks on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9647.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_059.tif)
- Fernando Munizaga coaches Slee Sinfonietta member Kristen Theriault, harp on Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias as Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Michael Tumiel, bass clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, bass flute look on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9648.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_060.tif)
- Fernando Munizaga coaches Slee Sinfonietta member Kristen Theriault, harp on Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias as Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Matsuno, bass flute, and Michael Tumiel, bass clarinet look on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9649.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_061.tif)
- Fernando Munizaga coaches Slee Sinfonietta member Kristen Theriault, harp on Munizaga's piece Ondas Primarias as Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass and Michael Matsuno, bass flute look on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9651.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_062.tif)
- Kezia Yap coaching Michael Matsuno, flute on Yap's piece A structure of silence: an exploration of Ma at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9656.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_063.tif)
- Michael Matsuno, flute rehearsing Kezia Yap's piece A structure of silence: an exploration of Ma at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9659.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_064.tif)
- Michael Matsuno, flute rehearsing Kezia Yap's piece A structure of silence: an exploration of Ma at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Michael.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_065.tif)
- Michael Matsuno, flute rehearsing Kezia Yap's piece A structure of silence: an exploration of Ma at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9664.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_066.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Hanna Hurwitz, violin, Will Knuth, violin, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00483.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_067.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Hanna Hurwitz, violin, Will Knuth, violin, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00484.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_068.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Hanna Hurwitz, violin, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00486.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_069.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Kristen Theriault, harp, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Stephen Solook, percussion, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Michael Tumiel, bass clarinet, Michael Matsuno, flute, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass in a performance of John Harbison's Mirabai Songs at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00489.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_070.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta member Tom Kolor, percussion performs Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9665.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_071.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta member Tom Kolor, percussion performs Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9666.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_072.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta member Tom Kolor, percussion performs Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9668.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_073.tif)
- Slee Sinfonietta member Tom Kolor, percussion performs Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney as composer David Felder looks on at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9671.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_074.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9673.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_075.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9674.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_076.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9675.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_077.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9676.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_078.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9677.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_079.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute acknowledge applause after a performance of Louis Karchin's piece Four Songs on Poems of Seamus Heaney at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9680.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_080.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Thomas Meglioranza, baritone, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute in performance of Louis Karchin's piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9683.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_081.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin shakes the hand of Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and acknowledges Slee Sinfonietta members Thomas Meglioranza, voice, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin, Tom Kolor, percussion, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Daniel Brottman, horn, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Michael Matsuno, flute after a performance of Karchin's piece Gods of Winter at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9684.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_082.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Kristen Theriault, harp, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass, and Michael Matsuno, flute before a performance of John Harbison's piece Mirabai songs at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9686.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_083.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Kristen Theriault, harp, Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Will Knuth, violin, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Michael Matsuno, flute, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass in a performance of John Harbison's piece Mirabai songs at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9688.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_084.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Will Knuth, violin, Stephen Solook, percussion, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Michael Matsuno, flute, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass in a performance of John Harbison's piece Mirabai songs at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9691.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_085.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin and Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano after a performance of Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9698.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_086.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin and Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano after a performance of Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9703.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_087.tif)
- Composer Louis Karchin and Tiffany DuMouchelle, soprano after a performance of Karchin's pieces at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Louis Ka.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_088.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Roger Reynold.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_089.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00500.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_090.tif)
- Irvine Arditti, violin rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00502.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_091.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds watches Irvine Arditti, violin rehearsing Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00504.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_092.tif)
- Paul Hembree, computer musician rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00505Paul H.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_093.tif)
- Paul Hembree, computer musician rehearsing Roger Reynolds' piece Shifting/Drifting at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DSC00509.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_094.tif)
- Su Lee, organist and composer, Jade Conlee, piano, and Tom Kolor, percussion rehearsing Lee's piece Nachruf für Nr. 503, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9770SU Lee.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_095.tif)
- Tom Kolor, percussion, Roberto Azaretto, and Christopher Guzman, piano talking during a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9776.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_096.tif)
- Composer Alon Nechushtan looking at his piece Three places in New York at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9781.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_097.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Jade Conlee, piano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin, Erin Lensing, oboe, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Jessica Wooldridge, bassoon, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Daniel Brottman, horn, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Sycil Mathai, trumpet, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass in a performance of William David Cooper's piece Epilogue at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9792.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_098.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Jade Conlee, piano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Erin Lensing, oboe, Jessica Wooldridge, bassoon, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Daniel Brottman, horn, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Sycil Mathai, trumpet, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass in a performance of William David Cooper's piece Epilogue at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9794.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_099.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor, leads Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth violin, Stephen Solook, percussion, Erin Lensing, oboe, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Jessica Wooldridge, bassoon, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Daniel Brottman, horn, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Tomek Arnold, percussion, Megan McDevitt, double bass, and Tom Kolor, percussion in a performance of Weijun Chen's piece Watercolors at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9797.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_100.tif)
- Composer Weijun Chen acknowledges Matthew Chamberlain, conductor and Slee Sinfonietta members Christopher Guzman, piano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth violin, Stephen Solook, percussion, Erin Lensing, oboe, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Jessica Wooldridge, bassoon, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Daniel Brottman, horn, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Tomek Arnold, percussion, Megan McDevitt, double bass, and Tom Kolor, percussion after a performance of Chen's piece Watercolors at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9799.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_101.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain, conductor leads Slee Sinfonietta members Jade Conlee, piano, Kristen Theriault, harp, Emlyn Johnson, flute, Hanna Hurwitz and Will Knuth, violin, Erin Lensing, oboe, Stephen Solook, percussion, Michael Tumiel, clarinet, Jessica Wooldridge, bassoon, Alyssa Roggow, viola, Daniel Brottman, horn, Katie Weissman, violoncello, Sycil Mathai, trumpet, Mark Broschinsky, trombone, and Tristan Kasten-Krause, double bass in a performance of William David Cooper's piece Epilogue at June in Buffalo 2018, 2018-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_9802.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0081_102.tif)